audioholics.com 2006-12-20

# Audioholics, Audio Product Reviews for the Masses

|  | 

_Where audio and video equipment undergoes rigorous objective and subjective tests by our staff, ensuring that marketing slogans aren't the only guidelines for your home theater choices._  
  
---|---  
  
|   
---  
 What to Buy - Our Picks  
 Set-Up Your System  
 How to Shop  
 Research AV Topics  
 Learn About Specs & Formats  
 Fix Your Room Acoustics  
 Get the Latest Industry News  
 Read A/V Editorials  
 Read Press Releases  
 Try a DIY Project  
 Latest Trade Show News  
 Frequently Asked Questions  
  
 Receivers & Amplifiers  
 DVD & Media Players  
 HDTV, Projectors & Displays  
 Cables & Power Conditioners  
 Loudspeakers  
 Misc Equipment & Software  
 DVD Movie Reviews  
 CD/SACD/DVD-Audio Discs  
  
 Buying Guides - How to Shop  
 Recommended Online Stores  
  
 Our Mission Statement  
 Our Reference Systems  
 Read Staff Bios  
 Recommended Manufacturers  
 Contact the Staff  
 Advertise With Us  
  
**Audioholics Supports**

**Audioholics Editorials**  
---  
  
Tuesday, December 12 2006  

Thursday, December 7 2006  

Saturday, December 2 2006  

Wednesday, November 29 2006  

Tuesday, November 28 2006  

Wednesday, November 22 2006  

Sunday, November 19 2006  

---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
**[Forums: Talk  
With Others](http://forums.audioholics.com/forums/)** | 

**Professional  
Product Reviews**

| **[Consumer  
Product Reviews](http://audioholics.audioreview.com/)** | **Learn About  
Cables & Power** | **Set Up Your  
AV System** | **Our Picks on  
What to Buy** | **[Find the Lowest  
Online Prices!](http://audioholics.pricegrabber.com/)**  
  
Audioholics has created this statement in order to communicate our firm commitment to privacy. We have taken the proper measures to ensure that your experience with us is safe, secure and enjoyable. This statement details our information gathering and sharing practices for Audioholics.

This Privacy & Security statement is subject to change without notice. We encourage you to review our Privacy and Security statement whenever you use this web site to make sure you understand how your information will be used.

Information We Collect and How We Use It  
Information Disclosure  
Links to External Sites  
Cookies  
Security   
Children's Guidelines  
Choice/Opt-Out  
Correct/Update  
Contacting Audioholics

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**  
When you visit our online forums, we may need to collect your name, e-mail address, and login information. This information allows us to process your membership and contact you if necessary. All of your information is stored on a secured server. If you do not wish to register your information online, you may not be able to take part in the online forum section of the website.

If you choose to participate in a contest or a promotion, we may ask for your name, address and phone number in order to administer the contest and notify the winners. If you volunteer to participate in an online survey, we may ask for contact information and possibly additional information such as your interests and demographics. Supplying this information is strictly voluntary. The information is used to provide you with a more personalized shopping experience, including future recommendations and promotions that may be of special interest to you. You may opt out of receiving this enhanced information if you so choose.

Information about your activity on the site is automatically collected when you sign in. We use this information to enhance and personalize your browsing experience. We monitor our site traffic patterns and site usage in order to improve the layout and design of our site. We use the information to notify you of any site changes, new features and services and to keep you informed of any special promotions offered by Audioholics and its affiliates. You may opt-out of receiving this information if you so choose.

To the extent that we use third party advertisers or contact lists to personalize your website experience, including future recommendations and promotions that may be of special interest to you, they may adhere to their own privacy customs and policies. Audioholics does not control the privacy policies of third parties and/or their opt out lists. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**Information Disclosure**  
When you utilize our online forums, we do not share any provided information with outside or third parties. We do not sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information with anyone outside of Audioholics.

We may provide your information as required by law or legal process; to protect and defend the rights of Audioholics, the Audioholics website or the users and, and under circumstances we believe reasonably necessary to protect the personal safety of users of Audioholics, this site or the public.

**Links to External and/or Co-Branded Sites**  
Our site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are not under our control. Audioholics is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. See our Terms of Service and Legal Notices. We do have co-branded sites with other companies. You should review those policies.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small piece of information that many Web sites use to help make shopping online easier. The information is stored on your computer's hard drive. It lets you shop our site, place items in your cart and return several days later without having to reenter the information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. Browsers usually provide the option to disable this feature.

**Security**  
Our site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Names, information and passwords are stored securely in areas of our server not accessible by the general public. No security is completely foolproof but we do our best to ensure that your information is secure.

**Children's Guidelines**  
At Audioholics, the safety of children is very important to us. We are committed to protecting the online privacy of children. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent. If you are under 13 and would like to register at Audioholics or provide personal information about yourself and your family, please ask a parent or guardian for assistance.

Audioholics cannot prohibit minors from visiting this site. Audioholics must rely on parents, guardians and those responsible for supervising children under the age of 13 to decide which materials are appropriate for such children to view and/or download.

Each time you view a page or download images or materials at Audioholics or provide information about yourself or your family, you are representing to Audioholics that you are 13 years or older.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
We offer you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request the information. Or, you may contact us in one of the following ways:

  1. You can send e-mail using our General contact form
  2. You can send us mail to:  
Audioholics  
Attn: Customer Care  
P.O. Box 1381, Tarpon Springs, FL 34688-1381

**Correct/Update**  
We provide several different methods for you to change or modify the information you give us by contacting us in one of the following ways, and providing the details of the information you wish to change:

  1. You can send e-mail using our General contact form
  2. You can send us mail to:  
Audioholics  
Attn: Customer Care  
P.O. Box 1381, Tarpon Springs, FL 34688-1381

**Contacting Audioholics**  
You may contact us if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site: 

  1. You can send e-mail using our General contact form
  2. You can send us mail to:  
Audioholics  
Attn: Customer Care  
P.O. Box 1381, Tarpon Springs, FL 34688-1381

**Top of Page**
